انا ماني شايف شي
ولا اني محتاج لي اي شي
ماني متاكد هل انا عايش
ولا في غرفه نوره مطفي
Am not taking LSDs
تلاقي Zero drugs on me
لاكن انا دايمن راسي ضارب
I really don't know what's on me
هل انا شايل هم اهلي
ولا شايل هم نفسي
هل انا خايف اني افقدهم
ولا خايف اكون وحيد؟
خايف اسيب الدنيه دي
و الناس بعده تنساني
ولا خايف اني اتعقب؟
هل جهزت لي اخرتي؟
In front of the mirror there I see
Someone I really think is me
هل انته تشوفو زي ما انا شايفو
ولا بختلف شكلو ليك؟
صوت في راصي قال لي اي
هل يعني? we all see different things
ولا انا قاعد اتوهم
اسمع نفسي الي ابي؟
قول ليx3
Do I have to change myself
or change the world around me
قول ليx3
Do I have to change myself
or change the world around me
*Change the world around me*
Am I losing myself?
Just to find myself
Cause I feel so alone Inside this zone
Do I want the money?
Do I want the fame?
Just to win this game
You should make a name
I wanna change it all
Put my back against the wall
The world is harsh and cruel
They love to see you fall
هل انا شايل هم نفسي ؟
ولا مو داري عن نفسي؟
ولا بارضي امي واهلي
ولا بارضي فيها حالي
لاني ضايع في الدنيا
ولسا اضيع كل ثانية
مو خالدين الحياة فانية
ولسا نضيع كل ثانية
ومني داري عن وقتي
زي ما اصبح صرت امسي
يومي صار زي امسي
طريقي ضايع بس امشي
مضيع اوقاتي مضيع صلاتي
هل راح اندم بعد مماتي ؟
واتمنى اعيد كل حياتي
واضحي بنفسي واضحي بمالي
صلح روحي اصلح حالي
اغير فكري اصفي بالي
اصلح الحاضر والماضي
عشان اكون مرتاح في مماتي
اصلح حالي x3
ما ارضى لحالي